# Chanh P. Ngo

 ♠ Alhambra, California, United States
 ■ pngo19@calstatela.edu
 □ (626) 877-3058
 In https://www.linkedin.com/in/fkvn/

https://github.com/fkvn

## **SUMMARY**

By picturing myself as a Full-Stack developer and concerning my long-term goals, I want to be an expert on the website development field, especially of progressive Web Applications. Besides, people who I've worked with are always willing to write a recommendation letter for me and give me a positive performance review. I'm proud to say that my secure communication, outstanding attitude, and impressive leadership skills set me apart from other programmers.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### TEACHING ASSOCIATE

CAL STATE LA - COMPUTER SCIENCE

- September 2020 Present, Los Angeles, CA
- 1. Grading homework and assignments for web development for java servlets and jsp.
- ullet 2. Maintained office hours frequently and support students for essential knowledges.
- 3. Having affordable skills and knowledges about web development fundamental for

#### ENTRY LEVEL ITS HELP DESK CONSULTANT

CAL STATE LA - ITS (IT CLIENT SUPPORT SERVICES)

- 1. Provided customer service and keep updated on ITS services available for campus users.
- 2. Assisted with the day-to-day operations within information Technology services.

#### ASSISTANT LAB CONSULTANT

CAL STATE LA - ITS (IT CLIENT SUPPORT SERVICES)

October 2018 — May 2020, Los Angeles,

May 2020 - Present, Los Angeles, CA

- $\bullet \ 1. \ Attend \ customer \ service \ and \ keep \ updated \ on \ ITS \ services \ available \ for \ campus \ users.$
- 2. Maintained lab services for software, security, and helping students most appropriately.
- 3. Devoted emphasis to punctuality, handling under pressure, and maintaining outstanding performance.

#### **DEVELOPER INTERN**

ISB VIETNAM COMPANY LIMITED (IVC)

- 1. Implemented multiple tasks related, mainly, to VBA for Microsoft Excel.
- 2. Primarily working on analyzing and implementing data from excel files to export expected results in terms of business/client demand.

July 2014 - October 2014, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **SURVEY SERVICE**

- 1. Provide the ability to conduct surveys for many systems, e.g. political campaigns, marketing research, and program assessment.
- 2. The service can be reused in another system as a standalone service.
- 3. Implemented in: Java, Maven, Spring-Boot, My SQL, REST API.

#### HIRING PROCESS SERVICE

- 1. Developed Rest API backend with Spring Boot application to build a hiring process service as a standalone service.
- 2. The service can be integrated into another system via a Rest API for any hiring purpose.
- 3. Implemented in: Java, Maven, Spring-Boot, My SQL, REST API.

#### POS SYSTEM SERVICE

- 1. Develop a server-side API service to facilitate the management process for a small-medium coffee shop.
- $\bullet 2. \ Owners\ can\ track\ hours, communicate\ with\ employees, and\ perform\ other\ tasks\ that\ help\ their\ store\ run\ smoothly.$
- 3. Implemented in: Node.js, Express, MongoDB, REST API.

# **EDUCATION**

#### **Master of Science in Computer Science**

CALIFORNIA STATE UNIVERSITY, LOS ANGELES · Los Angeles, CA, US · 2018 - Present · 4.0

#### **English Studies**

CALIFORNIA STATE UNIVERSITY, LONG BEACH (ALI) · Long Beach, CA, US · 2017 - 2018 · 4.0

#### **Bachelor of Science in Computer Science**

HO CHI MINH CITY, UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY · Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam · 2011 - 2016 · 3.1

#### **SKILLS**

Programming Languages: Java, JavaScript, Python

Front End: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, React Bootstrap, Redux

Back End: Spring-boot (Rest API), Nodejs, Express, MongoDB, MySQL

Technology/Software/Tool: Data Science, Machine Learning, Git, Eclipse, Vs Code

Additional Skills: Leadership, Collaboration, Adaptability, Critical Thinking, Problem Solving.

Languages: Vietnamese (Native or Bilingual), English (Full Professional), Chinese (Limited Working)

# LICENSES & CERTIFICATIONS

Become a spring developer – LinkedIn – Issued 2020

Become a MEARN stack JavaScript developer – LinkedIn – Issued 2020

MySQL essential training – LinkedIn – Issued 2020

# REFERENCES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST